marketwired.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy | Marketwired

##  Marketwired Privacy Policy 

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. By submitting personal information to us through your registration or otherwise by using our services, you agree that we may collect, use and disclose such personal information as described in and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted or required by law.

Your Consent and Changes 

By using our site and/or by using our services, you consent to our Privacy Policy and our collection, use, and disclosure of your information in accordance with it. If we make any substantive changes to our policies, we will notify you by posting notice of changes to this website. Your use of the site after the changes constitutes your agreement with regard to information collected from you in the past and in the future.

##  Information Gathered by Marketwired

For visitors to our website, subscribers to our newsletters, clients and prospective clients of our service (collectively referred to as a "User" or "Users"), we log standard technical information such as your IP address, interactions on different pages, and browser information. We use this information to help diagnose problems with our service, to administer our website and in reporting capacities as identified below to companies with whom Marketwired works, including its clients, partners, etc. For example, your IP address may be used to help identify you and your account information and to gather demographic information, or to maintain an aggregated log of click activity on our website.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your account. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to you.

We may also collect additional information from you when you fill out a form. Marketwired requires registration for certain services, such as the distribution of your press releases, and purchase of licenses to our Software-as-a-Service products. Our website may also contain order forms for other products and services or online surveys. In order to provide our services to you, we may ask you for contact information (such as name and email address), financial information (account or credit card numbers), mailing address, phone number, title, company name, and/or demographic information (including zip/postal code and age).

##  Marketwired's Use of Information

We may use your contact information to send you information about our company or our advertisers; however, you may opt out of receiving such mailings (see the Client Prospects and Subscribers sections below). We use financial information to bill you for products and services. Demographic, usage and profile data are also collected at our site, and may be used in the course of reporting. Anonymous user data (such as IP addresses, and/or their IP-location information, if available) may be utilized within aggregate traffic reporting to our clients. Additionally, certain information provided at user-registration (such as the name of a media outlet or user title) may be made available to clients within activity reports, although no personally identifiable information (such as names, phone numbers, or email addresses) will be reported.

We use this data to tailor your experience at our site, to deliver content that we think you might be interested in, to display the content according to your preferences and we may share aggregate information about our users with third parties such as advertisers or clients submitting press releases to Marketwired.

##  How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. However, it is possible that any information transmitted via the Internet may be intercepted by unknown third parties. We therefore encourage you to carefully ensure security through virus screening software, browser settings, the setting of passwords that are known only to you and are difficult to guess, and other security measures available to individuals and/or companies.

##  Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

##  Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information collected from visiting our websites [www.marketwired.com](http://www.marketwired.com/). This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

Marketwired may also disclose your personal information, the contents of your communications and/or your contact and financial information if required to do so by law, with your consent or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary:

  1. To conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on Marketwired;
  2. To protect and defend the rights or property of Marketwired or others; or
  3. To assist, under exigent circumstances, in the investigation of securities law violations or other investigations.

It is possible that as we continue to develop our business, Marketwired might be acquired. In such a transaction, your information may be transferred to the acquiring entity.

Additionally, we may store or process your personal information on servers in Canada and/or the United States. As a consequence, your personal information may be accessed by the courts, law enforcement and national security authorities of those jurisdictions in accordance with applicable laws.

By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password and/or user ID which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password or user ID with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access,

##  Advertisers and Other Third Parties

This site and some of our services contain links to other sites. Marketwired is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

We may use a third-party ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our website, cookies received with banner ads are collected by the third-party ad company, and we do not have access to this information. The privacy practices of companies who provide services or ads through our site are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please contact those companies directly for more information about their privacy practices.

##  Changes to Our Policies

Marketwired's Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we make any substantive changes to our policies, we will notify you by sending email to the address provided by you, or by posting notice of changes to this website. Your use of the site after the changes constitutes your agreement with regard to information collected from you in the past and in the future.

##  Security

We have in place industry standard security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control, including through the use of physical, organizational, and technological measures and appropriate training of employees. However, it is possible that any information transmitted via the Internet may be intercepted by unknown third parties. We therefore encourage you to carefully ensure security through virus screening software, browser settings, the setting of passwords that are known only to you and are difficult to guess, and other security measures available to individuals and/or companies.

##  Use by Minors Prohibited

Marketwired is not intended for and should not be used by anyone under the age of 18. Marketwired complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and does not permit registration or use by anyone under the age of 13.

##  International Users

If you are an international user, by registering with Marketwired or by using our service, you agree that we may collect, use and transfer your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you reside in the European Union or other jurisdictions that provide access rights under law, you may access your information or have it corrected or updated in accordance with applicable law by contacting us.

##  Clients

Clients who have registered in order to use our services can change or update their account information and preferences by:

  1. Visiting <https://www.marketwire.com/mw/clogin.do>;
  2. Calling Client Services at 800-774-9473; or
  3. Contact us

##  Client Prospects

From time to time we will email client prospects whom we have reason to believe might be interested in our services because of their involvement in the public relations, investor relations or related fields. Prospects can opt out of future communications simply by replying to the email and indicating their preference.

##  Subscribers

We provide subscribers to our email newsletters with the opportunity to opt out of receiving promotional communications at the point when we request your information. Additionally, subscribers have the right to mask the non-public registration details they provide (media outlet, city, state) from appearing within our activity reports. At any time, subscribers can change their preferences regarding promotional communications and reporting disclosures, can subscribe to or unsubscribe from any of our email newsletters and can modify other registration information previously provided to us by:

  1. Visiting Hot Off The Wire or
  2. Visiting Personal Beat or
  3. Using the link provided at the bottom of any email newsletter we send to you.

##  Social Media

From time to time we will participate in conversations on social media platforms such as [Twitter](http://www.twitter.com/Marketwired/), [LinkedIn](http://www.linkedin.com/company/18941), or [Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/marketwired/), where we have reason to believe individuals might be interested in our services because of their involvement in public relations, investor relations or related fields. Communications that are meant to be confidential in nature should be made through secure messaging options available within these third party websites/services. Questions about our social media policy should be forwarded to [info@marketwired.com](mailto:info@marketwired.com).

##  Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of Marketwired, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us at the postal address, phone number, fax number or email address listed below.

Marketwired, Inc.  
25 York Street  
Suite 900, P.O. Box 403  
Toronto, ON M5J 2V5  
Phone: 888-299-0338  
Fax: 416-362-5477  
Email: [info@marketwired.com](mailto:info@marketwired.com)

Last updated: May 20, 2013
